Screw it all away
Did you do it or not?
I'll take care of things later!
Oh, me, you bastard
Huh?
What should I do with you?
You idiot-like bastard
stand upright
Sorry!
- I'll take care of it.
-What do you do?
uh?
Even the one who caught it gets taken away, Mr.
Hey
Kim In-seop and
Because they seem to be related
Have the kids do a background check.
Me, you bastards
Let me live alone now
Are you doing this?
uh?
Looking after those who are discharged from the military
Is there anyone else besides me?
새끼들이 그냥, 씨
어?
Don't you listen to what I said? uh?
Minister
It's this guy
The guy who took Kim In-seop
Uh, you helped me find PD Kim.
They are local people
This is the president of the Changni-dong women’s association.
This is the youth president
Yes, that, youth president...
What kind of statement is there in this situation?
- Doyeon's father
- Yes
What on earth is here?
It's my first time here too...
This is Lee Geun-cheol, Vice Minister of National Defense.
This is Major Lee Soo-jin.
Ah, so...
So this is where
Safe house?
From the Ministry of Defense
In a case under investigation
Because Kim In-seop is involved
We decided to provide space
The price of oil is ridiculously high
‘It’s a strange gas station.’
I thought about it...
Hey, that was the operation, huh?
To keep people from coming
Right?
Me, Deputy Minister
Is there a place like this in every neighborhood?
It's a security thing...
Please sit down.
Ah, yes
- Fish oil
- What are you doing, man, what are you doing?
The bomb stolen from the military
It exploded in our neighborhood?
Yes
So the soldiers
So you came and cleaned it up like that? uh
I want to destroy the evidence.
Stolen bombs from the military
Is it possible?
Ah, even if I just steal the shell casings
There's an uproar
Hey, it doesn't make sense, but
It makes sense because this is the military again.
Who stole the bomb?
I'm looking into it.
PD Kim
Seeing as how I brought you here
It looks like quite a big deal is involved?
Huh, big guy?
President or
Isn't this the Minister of National Defense?
Hey, make sense.
When you watch a movie or drama
That's right
Hey, the president or the minister.
Why do such high-ranking people come here?
What do you do if you get hit?
Oh, if that's right, at our stationery store.
What you like best
take that toy
Are you here to play?
No...
like a toy
I'm making noise, really
Because of my brother
Even I got scolded.
This is amazing, hey
But Doyeon’s dad
yes
Deputy Minister of National Defense
How do you know?
Like a secret special agent or something
Maybe not?
Uh, that's...
Oh, wait a minute.
This is General Hwang.
Who is General Hwang?
- Kang is your brother’s sister-in-law.
- Uh
I have to go quickly now
Let’s talk in detail tomorrow at the bunker.
Okay, okay, come on in, uh.
Please go in
Uh, I'm on my way
It's in front of the house, in front of the house
Uh, uh
uh, bye
Then I...
We go too
Tell me everything you know
Sister, do you know JDD?
Oh, why?
just say
No, this is it, no comment...
After moving here
It's really strange
Me?
It's not
before you
Wasn’t it work, home, work, home?
Since when is it on your daily schedule?
A lap around the neighborhood was added?
So that's it
The youth president, that person...
Change your repertoire
Always the youth leader
It's insincere.
Wash and sleep
yes
Hey
Hey, didn’t you get scolded by Jesu?
My sister-in-law was okay.
Yeah?
You have that camera.
Something that looks like a button
My masterpiece that you lost?
I didn't lose it
I planted it on a mercenary's clothes.
its last location
Can you find it?
Are there any useful clues in it?
It might have been filmed
You can find out who's behind it, huh?
Hey, Mr.
It went off last night
Did it turn off because there was no battery?
That's a one-month supply.
I found out where it went off.
Did you find it? where are you?
Why are you going alone again?
Then shall we go together?
Am I the only one who knows this place?
- Mistress
- Baby, give it to me.
Ah, really, why are you like this?
- Hey, sleep, wait, huh?
- Are you coming together? Give it to me quickly!
Go together, go together, then
Needle
What are you doing there this morning?
Uh, nothing.
Ah...
Ah, Byeongnam’s younger brother
The weather is a mess
I got some discipline, brother.
Hahaha!
See you at lunch
Yes
Oh, I'm at work
I'm going to work
uh
What for lunch, what?
Hey, what are you guys going to do?
Me too, put me in, put me in too
Hehe, what are you doing?
Because it's nothing
Hey, you all except me last night...
Uh, Nam, Namyeon, uh
Hey, man, where are you going, you bastard!
Oh, not honey.
Uh, uh, I'll be there right now, uh
Honey, I'll be right away, honey.
I'll be there right away
uh
Baby, it's late, am I?
why?
Uh, at a safe gas station.
Another order came? uh?
He went there with his kids yesterday.
At that safe gas station
really
Oh, really
Aren't you going to tell me? uh?
huh? what?
No, with Yonghee
With a sick man and a tutor
Why did you go to the gas station? I...
stop asking
Just ask me one more time, tsk
Delivery!
Oh, yes, thank you!
I think that was a flyer from Changri Market.
Turn that around when you deliver it.
Is it okay to ask?
Wow, really
generally
What about insurance investigators?
Hire a professional
Because we have to catch those who are scamming people.
Detective, lawyer, nurse, etc.
But this kid is the strongest
I was exempted from military service after dropping out of college.
You were unemployed and then joined the company?
Without a major?
You get the feeling right, right?
But
Choi Kang goes to Vertigo Insurance.
It took government money.
What, private corporate investment or something like that?
no
It is a subsidy for R&D and defense industry from the Ministry of National Defense.
Also from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
No, the Ministry of Defense's defense industry subsidies
Does the Ministry of Foreign Affairs provide support?
what is that
It's not like there isn't much
That's not common though
Since when?
if
After this guy joins the company?
yes
It's a subsidy, but there's no end date.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
Hey, I used to
The Ministry of Foreign Affairs only distributes it overseas.
I heard there is a unit
Where do you think I heard that?
Ah, then
Aren't you part of the Ministry of Defense?
Hey
Dig this properly
Ah, yes
Did you recognize the Kiyun City bomb?
No, I had a hard time sending it out.
Why did you come back again?
Oh, that's it
I bought it locally and paid twice as much.
Brokers can't contact me
Please wait a moment.
How long will you wait, Mr. Lee?
But brother
Lee Geun-cheol
They're digging for the bomb.
I have a story
Lee Geun-cheol?
yes
Are you here?
Are you busy these days?
yes?
Moving around here and there
There was a rumor
Even if not
I had something to report to you.
Reporting?
suddenly?
Military supplies from our military
It exploded in a civilian area
It seems like there was corruption in the defense industry.
Oh, really?
Minister on this matter
Do you have anything to say?
uh?
With the money from stealing weapons and selling them
I invested in Changni-dong.
The weapon is back
They're strangling the minister.
That's not important
I think Lee Geun-cheol knows.
Minister at that time
Just shouting at me
Didn't you?
My brother said he would take care of everything.
Ah, who doesn't take care of it?
Anyway, I am a member of the National Assembly too.
I don't know everything
So a little bit
Let's help each other, that's what I'm saying
Each other?
Oh, really
Ah, why are you so stiff? uh?
This is wrong, right?
Then we all die together
I do this even though I know everything.
Chairman
This is Naeunjae
Let's have a meal
Uh, hey, here
Yo, yeah, yolo all the way
Yeah
Well, no comment.
That
Commented to Mammoth
child
What a mouthful, ah
Hey, what should I do if they say they're going to kill me?
Well, is there a way? I came that far
Hey, by the way, I
Uh, I have a question.
500 won if you’re curious
Yay
Cut it down
Then 300 won
You...
Why did you go to JDD?
To make money
Is it over?
If you have any additional questions, 200 won
Hey Mr. Lee!
Wow, Mr.
Don't do it, don't do it
Fish oil! Really, Mr.
Did you lose the signal because of that?
Looks like a regular transceiver?
I used a cheap GPS chip.
I guess it bounced because there was a lot of signal.
Ah, in this wide place
How do you find that little button?
Even if GPS is turned off
The recording function will be fine.
What if it goes off together?
It must have been recorded until it was turned off.
Ah, in the old days
If an electronic device breaks down, get hit several times.
If that doesn't work, turn the power off and on.
Then it went well
Everything is digital these days
- That's it.
- What?
Hey
So you can turn it off and on.
Hey, that's it!
What, did I solve it?
If recording continues
Because there is nothing wrong with the machine
All you have to do is reset the GPS signal.
Who are you talking to? scary
Hey, there must be a way to find it.
Follow me
Did you find a way?
- What is it?
- Follow me.
Oh, will it be over soon?
Uh, uh
inside that button
What was captured?
Their hideout
Or
Who's behind them?
Ah, if you play this during labang
It's game over
Aren’t you scared of them?
It's scary
But if you hide because you’re scared
Then they won't do it again.
yes
They said the GPS was turned off
How do I retrieve it?
Well, I'm simple
Make a piece of equipment
I'm going to turn it off and on.
Brother
By no means send a signal
Reset GPS error?
Oh, you're smart too, huh?
Then go quickly and make it
I'm going to make it
I have another problem
The industrial complex
It's a bit wide
Then
Things like RC cars and drones
How about using it?
there
Put on a reset device and search for it.
Uh, definitely
It must be faster than people.
There are a lot of wires
Wouldn’t an RC car be better than a drone?
Even more than that
This, what
Useful RC cars are quite expensive.
home
I have two
Then one
I'll airlift
Let's go to three
Then practice driving
Let's each do our own thing
Let's disperse
- That's a good idea.
- thank you
let's go
What is it?
Well, no, no, please give me a laptop.
Can I bring it?
Here
I think the radio waves are completely blocked.
yes
thank you
RC unit 3 is waiting for deployment
When identifying target position
Infiltration Team One Squad
It is scheduled to be deployed
The remaining units are
With rear standby and situation-specific QRF
I'm planning on switching
Wow, Yonghee.
What is this...
yes, i understand
loyalty
Is that it?
Uh, yeah
This is the laptop I mentioned back then.
Where can I put it!
Give it to me
Ah, yes
Ah, Sujin.
I just saw that...
This is a situation report.
Ah
I guess things are a bit like that these days.
So?
Uh, so
Uh, some context.
I think it's cool
You did a really good job reporting.
There's good news and bad news
Oh, the good news first.
We provide equipment support for this operation.
wow! Hey!
So what's the bad news?
If you come dressed like that again
I'll kill you
yes
Why are you asking for bad news?
Ha, really
hello
I'm trying to find some clothes
I still wondered why you didn’t come
Kang left it to me before.
You came here to pick up a jacket, right?
yes
Do you remember what clothes they are?
Oh, then
How long has it been since you made a living from this?
Now
- Well, it costs 10,000 nyang.
- Yes
Oh my, our Doyeon
You just get prettier every time I see you, right?
thank you
- Here.
- Wow
Have you finished organizing your moving items?
Before, Kang had a lot of baggage.
The box is still not organized
I heard there is one
Uh, my husband
Did you even say that?
Doyeon's mother
Do you know how scary it is?
Me?
Oh, by the way, I said all sorts of things, really.
Our Doyeon is a burden
It's just one piece, right?
It's like that in all homes with kids, right?
Ah
To our Doyeon
Clothes that no longer fit
If there is a toy you no longer play with
Give it to Changri Market.
Changri Market?
Oh, you don't know yet.
This is what the local women’s club does.
Well, we share things with each other.
I also eat snacks
Now the local people
It's good to learn the face too.
Our Doyeon makes a friend.
yes
- thank you
- Okay, okay, let's go.
- Yes
- Goodbye.
- Draw, go.
- Yes
Huh? It's a man
hello uncle
Oh, Doyeon!
Doyeonah
hello
Ah, because the river is my wife
Is it okay if I call you Mr. Jesu?
Oh, you are the boss, right?
Yes, I'm the boss here
my wife
This is the captain and that's right.
Ah, that kimchi stew with curry.
I guess you want to do it
How did you know?
Kang was very proud.
Jesu has his own secret recipe.
Oh, I'm talking about all sorts of things.
I'm just talking about life, you know?
- Choose comfortably
- Yes
To mom
Please buy me something delicious
- Yes
- Okay.
let's go
Yeah
Doyeon, hello
Minseo, hello
Oh my
Doyeon’s mom, what are you doing tomorrow?
No, if you're not busy
I'd like to invite you here
Oh, Changri Market?
The laundromat owner said
Ah, as expected, our bank manager.
If nothing happens, I'll come with Doyeon.
Is Minseo coming too?
Maybe he'll come after tutoring?
The hotteok there is really delicious.
- Hotteok?
- Yes
mom, i want to go
I want to go, I want to go
- Shall we go then?
- huh!
Ahh, hotteok
Hotteok, hotteok
Sounds delicious, hotteok
With the supermarket owner’s daughter
When did you become friends?
Wow, he’s very local.
I'm friendly with everyone
And with dad
Our director is also very close.
We always whisper together
It's a big deal, really.
my words
I just won't rest my mouth
We're all here
Huh?
It's the car in front of the laundromat.
Let's go up
Yeah
Why did you call me?
Are you here, Agent Black?
What do you think?
What is that?
Weight 350g, length 32cm
Used by special forces around the world
Because it was made with average specifications
It'll be comfortable
Uh, when there's this
Think of it as a three-tiered pole and use it.
And when it's closed
Did you see that movie? uh?
'What do you mean?'
I thought it was an axe or a hammer.
Just take a picture of it all
Then the corn just goes out.
Now
Wow
Hey, isn't it awesome?
That's right
uh
near and far
both are useful
Wait a minute, can't it be...
Huh?
Does it also have an electric shock function?
Ah, what are you talking about?
I left out the sound because I was afraid it wouldn't suit me.
Ah
First of all, the visual
Yeah
- Passed
- Yes! under!
Hey
Turn it off and on What about the GPS receiver?
Oh, don't worry about that.
Did you put a GPS receiver in this?
Uh, right
I went to the industrial complex to scout during the day.
Oh, I'm ready
Because it's Saturday
There are many companies that take a break.
Oh, it's a 5-day work week.
It's a given.
There are a lot of empty factories
Ah, the economy is bad these days.
Don't criticize me and listen
Okay
I'll take care of everything tomorrow.
Huh? When you find the location
Do you want to go right in?
So should I go at night?
How to control an RC car
The day is nice
Tomorrow is Changri Market.
It's a bit hard to leave during the day...
Reconnaissance team goes during the day
The entry team can go at night.
Then no problem
Then Doyeon’s father
Enter the starting line
I'll support you from the rear
yes
But this receiver
How does it work?
Uh, it's simple.
If you turn it on and run when you leave
The GPS will receive a signal and reset.
Then the location will appear on your phone again.
I go in and retrieve it.
The vice president is backing up.
Yeah
With this
You can also communicate here
How?
It connects to the bunker computer.
oh
And this is a listening device
- Oh
- Wow, isn't that cool?
- Let’s try it on first.
- Yes
yes
When designated as a special disaster area
You can make it happen quickly.
Because I have a reason
Whether it’s government support or tax benefits.
All you have to do is push hard.
It has to be there but
Because there has to be a disaster of that magnitude.
Terrorism
It's a social disaster.
national well-being and social order
You're threatening me.
The residents of my district are anxious.
I'm on the verge of becoming neurotic.
Why are you so tight?
The scale of damage is key.
Ki Yun-si said that was ambiguous.
My son hasn’t had any accidents lately.
Are you doing well?
uh
Oh, how are you?
Oh my, I have this
I forgot to say hello.
Greetings
Let's say I got it
When it comes to disaster areas
Please do your best
Your son is very unlucky too.
Even if there was an accident, Sullivan's daughter was killed.
But it's hard for us too
Supreme Court ruling
Because Sullivan did not invest
public sentiment
Because it’s such a mess
Uh, I'm out.
Bring the car
uh? Maybe...
"James Sullivan"
honey
Are we moving again?
I'm going to take it to Changri Market tomorrow.
Ah, Changri Market
It is hosted by a women’s association.
They say it's really fun
That's right
let's go too
I ate out in the evening for the first time in a while.
Do I have plans for dinner tomorrow?
Do you have an appointment with the youth leader on the weekend?
No, that's not it...
Or it's okay
Going to Changri Market tomorrow
people in your neighborhood who are close to you
say hello to me
The bank manager and the supermarket owner
They were all good people
Doyeon is also pretty.
I'm trying to become closer too.
Well, tomorrow evening
It's not a promise to the youth leader...
Cancel it, huh?
Don't look at me anymore
Okay
Ah, that's enough
Change your clothes
Brother, let’s get on.
Hey, is this a car you haven’t seen before?
It's a second car.
As expected, uh, it’s dope.
- Let's go
- I'm leaving.
uh
thank you
Look look
- I'll park and go.
- Yes
let's go
- There is.
- Yes
Doyeon, don’t run.
yes
Huh? Doyeon’s mom is here?
- Yes, hello.
- Hello
I'm going to share this
Where should I put it?
Oh, hey, just take it from me.
Doyeon's mom
Sit here and eat some dried persimmons
It's really delicious
Let's eat first, please
Come on, let's eat
It looks so delicious
Well!
It's really delicious
- Is it delicious?
- Yes
Mmm, it's really delicious
Ah, it’s Sangju dried persimmon.
Well, dried persimmons are a staple, hmm!
My relative is Sangju.
- Oh, really?
- Yes
I must have eaten a lot
And please feel free to speak now.
um
Is that so?
- coffee
- thank you
Try it, it's so delicious
- Is it delicious?
- It's delicious.
But who is the youth president?
Oh, my husband
We talked so much
I'd like to say hello
Oh, youth president?
Wow, that's right
Well, where did you go? I can't see it
- Um...
- Where did you go?
What about Yongmu Dojang Director?
Oh my, oh my
- Now that I think about it, I can’t even see Yonghee.
- Yes
So, where has everyone gone?
Eat, eat
Isn't it delicious?
It's so delicious
Huh? Wait a minute
uh
How is the situation around you?
It's perfect weather for driving
Don't worry, just take care of the village.
See you later
You practiced a lot, right?
- Yes, I practiced all night.
- Yes
Shall we begin?
Yeah
Don't go too fast
Time to transmit radio waves
Because I have to have it
At what speed should I go?
Awesome speed?
"Departure"
Huh?
IC
Why?
Ai, ah, this doesn’t work.
What are you doing, pick it up and run
Ah!
That, that, anyway
You didn't practice at all, that, Mr.
Oh my, that's right
Ah, ah!
- uh? Brother...
- Yayi
- Go, I'll come back.
- Yes
Mr. A, everything is ruined, Mr.
receiver
Okay
What is it?
uh?
oh
Is it here?
uh? I found it
Brother, I found it.
Did you find it?
- Yes
- Okay
Hey, hey, then put up a wiretap.
Yes, brother
Okay
Where are you, where? uh?
Uh, hey, man.
Me?
Ah, why
Do you feel embarrassed carrying someone else’s RC car?
Ah
Owner?
What are you doing here?
Oh, well, let's practice driving, okay?
Ah, this is the place on the weekends
It’s a mecca for driving practice.
Go somewhere else and do it
Hey, pull out.
withdrawal
Brother, nice
- Hey, Yonghee.
- Yes?
- Take this.
- Why, brother?
You guys go first
What about you, brother?
Until I enter the team
I'll sulk here
- I'll come back quickly.
- Uh, see you later.
yes
Wait a minute
- Yes
It's really delicious, right?
They said they found the button location.
Uh, I heard.
Hey, clean up after yourself.
Because Minseo’s dad will do it
We'll be leaving soon
Oh, I guess I'll be a little late.
What should I buy you? this?
Because of Doyeon’s mom?
yes
Let's leave separately
If an error occurs twice
Access is blocked
Boy, really
Sujin, I am from the 900 unit.
That's amazing
Okay
"Login"
“Connection complete”
Okay
“Connect”
Can you see it? It's coming out
uh
Hey
Soccer A match is today, right?
yes, that's right
It's 8 o'clock today
Hey, the Korea-Japan match again
Shouldn’t we see it?
Hey, later
Hey, order a beer and something to eat.
yes, i understand
oh
Nice, I can hear you well.
Ah, ah, can you hear me?
Uh, I can hear you
Hey, when is the entry team coming?
I've arrived at the market now
Yes, I will pick you up right away.
Uh, I'll be arriving soon, so I'll see you at the entrance.
- Brother
- Uh
What about Brother Kang?
Uh...
I think it'll be a little late
Hey, drinking beer
I think I'm going to watch soccer
Should I wait until it stretches out?
No, I have to go in.
Brother
What is the operation?
Chicken in soccer
Delivery has arrived!
Ah, yes, delivery has arrived.
Ah, here...
yes it is here
Ah...
card?
- Ah...
- What about card machines?
doesn't exist?
I brought it with me, but no, no...
Ah, where did this go?
Wait a minute
Transfer money to account
Oh, bank transfer?
Oh yes, thank you
child, thank you
Ah, 91
- 9...
- No, 91
- 1?
- Yes, 8
Huh?
uh? Brother
There's real delivery out there, real delivery
- Huh? delivery?
- delivery?
Delivery!
You’re pig’s feet, right?
Here
Hey
Did you bring a card machine?
Who...
- Yes?
- card machine
- Oh, yeah.
- Give it to me quickly.
Uh, okay, I'll take the card.
Uh, wait...
Is it chicken?
I ordered pig's feet?
yes?
It's a one plus one event
So, if you order pig’s feet,
Chicken is free!
bon appetite!
I went there
10,100, 18,000...
Hey, wait a minute
Hey
- Mini car
- Yes?
- Right?
- yes? What are you saying...
- Take it off, take it off.
- What is it? Well, what...
Take it off, take it off!
No, mister! president! eww!
You're clueless, Mr.
Lady, what are you doing here?
Shut up and attack me
honey
- Doyeon's father
- Huh?
why?
What should we eat for dinner?
Oh, I don't care about anything
Do you care that much?
uh?
- Hey, come to work.
- Yes?
- Come quickly, come to work.
- No, no.
- Ah, boss.
- Come to work.
Come to work, come to work, come to work!
Ah, this bastard!
Ana, you son of a bitch.
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, put that down
Put it down, put it down, put it down
- Hey, put that down.
- Put it down.
Wow!
and! and!
Are you crazy, should I just get caught?
- Come at me, come at me, Mr.
- Come at me, come at me
Hey, come at me
Huh? uh?
Internal situation occurs
Byeongnam, are you okay?
Jeonghwan, with Byeongnam’s brother
Namyeon noona has no answer
I have to go back up
Back up!
Me?
Yeah, ah, right now, right now
I'll go right away
Come on, you bastards!
Hey, Jeonghwan
Brother, are you okay?
Why are you here, man?
Hey
Mother!
Hey Mammoth, are you okay?
I am a former artilleryman in the Republic of Korea...
Oh, really that one, Mr.
Jeonghwan, what happened?
Byeongnam’s older brother, Namyeon’s older sister!
Oh, someone please answer this, okay?
Ai!
Atta
This lady is really nice, huh?
Hey, relax your neck
Uh oh
Stop hitting me, stop hitting me
Speak up when asked nicely
What are you!
No, don't hit me
If you hit me, don't ask, okay?
I guess it's okay if I hit him good?
- Mistress
- Hey
Just deal with it.
What do you handle? yes?
- Deal with it.
- Yes?
- Let's go
- No, there, there...
Let go
Let's go, okay?
Doyeon Dad!
River!
older brother!
Am I too late?
fish oil, seeds
Wow, it's done
Oh no
It's not late at all
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
catch
I'm behind
Uh, hey
Hey, are you okay?
Vice President, are you okay?
yes, i'm fine
Doyeon's Dad
AC
Is everyone okay? yes?
Uh, it's okay
Oh my, really
Contact us early too
Sister, at the entrance
I got GPS
Is there a room near the entrance?
Oh my, my legs hurt so bad
What is it?
Is it a button?
I found it
Huh? wow!
nice!
Let it go, let it go
Nice! Let go
Hey!
Hey, but
Why are you here so late?
The story is long
Doyeon's mom
What did you say?
That's not what I said.
Doyeon's mother
Save everything and take a long time
went and came
I don't know what it is
I think it's something you need
Can I really go?
Don't get hurt instead
Don't be late
Because Doyeon is waiting for you to come
Okay
What happened?
I'm not sure
Nothing was stolen, nothing was robbed...
Hey, you bastard
What are these bastards doing?
Are we here to fight Daguri, then?
I think you should come and see for a moment.
What is it again?
take a look at this
What is it, you bastards?
to?
what's this?
what?
fish oil
Hey, this...
What is this?
no
dark and
Well, they all look the same
This is most certain
Oh, really, man, Mr.
It's you, really
This...
Lady, this...
I ripped it all off
This is it
Now, uh
Turn it on
I am Inseop Kim
Get rid of it
I did it!
Are you guys going to do your work like this?
Bomb related niggas, bomb related
I told you not to leave everything behind.
Hey, what should I do with you?
uh?
Is that kid the criminal?
I see you talking about bombs and blah blah.
That person is right
sorry
I will handle it
Huh?
uh?
That person...
Why?
Do you know someone?
Wow
Who is it?
Seokjun Kim
I am the Minister of National Defense.
But what about Mom and Dad?
meet a friend
Friends?
At this time?
uh?
It's the ice cream guy.
PD Kim was taken away
Did you really not know he was a minister?
Knowing everything from the beginning
Did you approach me on purpose?
Minister of National Defense of the Republic of Korea
I barely managed to steal a few bombs
Would you commit corruption?
These kids
Why are you coming to someone else's neighborhood?
This is why finishing is important
In Changni-dong
Who set off the bomb?
What are you going to do with that?
Prepare a bomb
Let Kiyun City explode
Brother, run away quickly!
No
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri